let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: 'Which technology will most influence workplaces in 2025?',
    answer: 'Artificial Intelligence ğŸ¤–',
    options: ['Blockchain â›“ï¸', '3D Printing ğŸ–¨ï¸', 'Artificial Intelligence ğŸ¤–', 'Quantum Computing âš›ï¸'],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: 'Which AI tool is widely used for content generation in 2025?',
    answer: 'ChatGPT ğŸ¤–',
    options: ['Photoshop ğŸ–Œï¸', 'ChatGPT ğŸ¤–', 'Zoom ğŸ¥', 'Excel ğŸ“Š'],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: 'Which skill is considered essential for almost every career?',
    answer: 'Communication ğŸ—£ï¸',
    options: ['Speed reading ğŸ“–', 'Drawing âœï¸', 'Communication ğŸ—£ï¸', 'Memorization ğŸ§ '],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: 'Which platform is known for professional networking and resumes?',
    answer: 'LinkedIn ğŸ’¼',
    options: ['Instagram ğŸ“¸', 'SnapChat ğŸ«°', 'LinkedIn ğŸ’¼', 'Facebook ğŸ‘'],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: 'Which tech skill is in high demand across industries?',
    answer: 'AI & Machine Learning ğŸ¤–',
    options: ['Data Analytics ğŸ“Š',
      'AI & Machine Learning ğŸ¤–',
      'Cloud Computing â˜ï¸',
      'Cybersecurity ğŸ”’',],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: 'Best way to structure your daily tasks?',
    answer: 'Prioritize important tasks ğŸ˜',
    options: ['Start with random tasks ğŸŒ€', 'Rely on memory ğŸ§ ', 'Prioritize important tasks ğŸ˜', 'Complete only easy tasks ğŸ˜´'],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: 'Who is known as the father of computers?',
    answer: 'Charles Babbage ğŸ’»',
    options: ['Alan Turing ğŸ¤–', 'Charles Babbage ğŸ’»', 'Bill Gates ğŸªŸ', 'Steve Jobs ğŸ'],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: 'Which approach improves productivity when working remotely?',
    answer: 'Set clear goals ğŸ¯',
    options: ['Switch tasks constantly ğŸ”„', 'Check messages often ğŸ“©', 'Set clear goals ğŸ¯', 'Keep email notifications on ğŸ””'],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: 'What does â€œDMâ€ stand for on most social apps?',
    answer: 'Direct Message ğŸ“©',
    options: ['Data Monitor ğŸ“Š', 'Direct Message ğŸ“©', 'Digital Media ğŸ’»', 'Download Manager ğŸ“¥'],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: '5 people paint 5 walls in 5 hours. How many walls can 10 people paint in 10 hours?',
    answer: '20',
    options: ['25', '15', '20', '10'],
  },
];
